The sky of the starry sky
The sky of the stars
Daytona
In your imagination
You will never forget
A bullet in a pas
I wonder what you and I
onboard you
The time when the light shines
The picture of the light is connected
You and you, you and you
If you love me, if you love me
I will be able to be with you for a long time
I don't feel like I'm going to be able to do it
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
I can do it, too!
Let's go to school!
Well, I've finished my lesson!
Honestly, I don't need that.
If you're sorry, then...
Hm?
Takakura-kun?
Hey!
You're a fool!
Takakura-kun, are you still here?
I didn't expect you to be here.
But...
I want to ask you a favor.
You're...
Huh?
Oh!
I'm sorry!
Why are you so angry at me?
I'm sorry.
Ah...
Anyway, you don't have to worry about your job.
If you don't study properly, you'll be in trouble.
Got it?
Oh...
Well, then.
I'll ask you a question for the next class.
The teacher is so young.
I can't do that.
No, I'm not.
I'm a teacher.
The teacher of school is not that simple.
Takakura-kun!
You're right, right?
You're right.
Mr. Shikata?
Oh, yes.
If you have a reason to talk to me,
you can ask me a question.
Okay!
Okay.
B!
I don't think I can do that.
I see.
Are you tired?
Takakura-sensei?
You're going to be in trouble.
Even if you want to get angry at me,
you can't do it as a teacher.
Why don't you study properly at that time?
Thank you very much.
Are you tired?
Yes!
Today, I'm going to be in trouble.
Look!
Wow!
It's much better than I thought.
Wow! It's amazing!
It's a lot better than I thought.
Well, I'm going to be in trouble
because I'm going to be in trouble.
Is that so?
I'm going to be in trouble because I'm going to be in trouble.
I understand.
It's so strange.
What's wrong with my drawing?
Takakura-kun?
Huh?
Mr. Shenzu?
Is it a school in the office?
Well, I'm going to be in trouble.
Hey, this is a good school.
I'm going to be in trouble.
I'm going to be in trouble because I'm going to be in trouble because I'm going to be in trouble.
I'm sorry.
What's with the school?
What's going on?
What are you doing?
Mr. Shenzu, you're scared.
Huh?
I'm scared.
You, should I go to school tomorrow?
Huh?
Do you want to go to school?
Oh, is it okay to be in trouble?
I want to go to school because I'm going to be in trouble.
Hey, you're going to be in trouble because I'm going to be in trouble?
I'm not saying that.
I'm going to be in trouble because I'm going to be in trouble because I'm going to be in trouble.
That's good.
Come on, let's go.
Mr. Shenzu, what are you girls doing?
That's a big deal.
A big deal?
Hey, Mr. Shenzu.
Right, I don't think I'll be able to do anything with you.
Mr. Shenzu.
Hey, you are late.
Mr. Shikata is actually in trouble.
Huh?
Hey, you, your mom is in trouble because you are in trouble.
Here you go.
Nyaaah!
Ah!
Oh, it wasn't before the fire didn't work!
Did you hear something?
Yes, I did!
But now, the animals can also be connected, so they won't work!
That's right!
Oh, that's good. What's the matter with you, Otomari-doshi?
Oh, the business is starting.
Hey, Yuka-chan, let's go to the first class.
I'll give you some delicious food.
No, it's a bit scary.
Why?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
I'm here, Mr. Seifi.
Right, I'm good.
Eh, your calories side up now, nothing to cry about.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I'm more potatoes enough, more potatoes, more potatoes.
Look, look at this, so it's good as well right now.
Hello.
Huh?
What's wrong with you?
I'll give you a hug.
You'll give me a hug?
I don't think so.
Please give me a hug.
Yes!
Ah!
Santa!
Did you get this?
Did you get it?
I did it.
It's too late.
Santa is so big.
He doesn't know how to do it.
Look!
I'm giving you a hug!
What are you doing here?
I'm dead.
Taka, Taka, Santa!
It's too late.
I can't do this anymore.
I'm a teacher, so I have to do my best.
I'll do my best.
What's wrong with you?
Ah, teacher Kyoto.
I have a lot of time.
Do you have a word to say about that?
I don't know.
I'm an expert at the school.
I don't know how to say that.
I'm sorry.
Wait!
Please return to the center of the planet!
Santa, you're the savior!
That's what I said!
Today's event is about 2,000 to 3,000,000 years ago.
It's the time to say that it's the center of the universe of 6,000 to 5,000 years ago.
It's really a nightmare.
Hold on!
Wow!
I'm so excited!
Hold on!
What are you doing?
I'm going to take care of this black hole.
I'll take care of it.
That rabbit!
Use that rabbit!
It's not a rabbit, it's a dinosaur!
What?
I'm going to take care of this black hole!
Please return to the center!
Muka Muka!
I'm not going to play here!
I'm going to take care of this black hole.
What?
Did you bring it to the center?
I...
I brought it to the center of the universe!
What are you doing?
I'm thinking of what to do.
Please don't do that, Mr. Yoshikawa.
I have a man in this world.
Mr. Koda.
I've been searching for him since I was born.
What?
I'm going to take care of him since I was born.
I'm going to take care of him.
That's fine.
Where's Mr. Wabuki?
He's right here.
I'm going to take care of him.
I'm going to take care of this black hole.
He's just like a kid.
I'm going to take care of him.
Mr. Yoshikawa.
We're doing a good job, Mr. Yoshikawa.
You guys are good.
Mr. Yoshikawa, please.
Yes, Mr. Yoshikawa.
I'm going home.
That's all for today.
Are you going to take care of him?
I don't think I got it right now, but I don't think everyone's going to get it right, so I'm going to promise it.
Promise? Is that okay?
Yes.
Is there something wrong?
No, but...
Well, the teacher will be ready for the next lesson.
Hey!
What's going on?
What's wrong with the school?
Hey!
It seems like this guy is getting angry.
Hey, Muka Muka!
Did you get the teacher's power?
That's because...
It's because Muka Muka got the teacher's power because Muka Muka got the teacher's power.
What?
Well, the teacher's power is because Muka Muka got the teacher's power.
What are you doing?
Are you going to get it right?
Well, well, well, I'm not going to get it right.
No, I'm not going to get it right.
I'll do it.
Hey!
I didn't say anything wrong.
It seems like it.
Huh?
Muka Muka?
Where did you go?
Huh?
Ah!
Can you get the competition?
Probably not.
Hurry!
This is so fun!
It's more fun!
Oh! Sister!
Sister!
Hey! Sister!
Sister! Are you all right?
I didn't know about the past.
Oh!
It's a big deal!
What's going on?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Is it a big deal?
What are you saying?
You always get angry at the teacher.
You're always like this, right?
You're always like this.
Are you all right?
I'm always angry at the teacher.
You're always angry at the teacher.
Of course.
I'm not wrong.
What?
I've thought that when I was a eder, I was a teacher.
I thought that it was a hot and warm dough, right?
I think it was because of the girl.
If my mother were alive, it was the girl.
My mother was crying as she was crying.
I wanted you to cry.
I'm sorry! That's not true!
Muka Muka?
There are some bad things to do in here.
Do you hear me, Muka Muka?
It's just that!
Don't you know that Muka Muka doesn't like humans?
What do you mean by that?
Eh?
Well, that's...
It's just that I don't have anything to say.
Humans have their own way of living.
I like it.
If you say that,
Muka Muka doesn't want to live with people.
If you really live,
Don't you know that Muka Muka doesn't like it?
Hmm...
Muka Muka doesn't like to live with people.
Muka Muka doesn't like it.
Huh?
What is it?
It's a teacher!
Teacher!
Huh?
Ah...
That's right, teacher!
I like it.
Look at Muka Muka.
It looks like Muka Muka is scared.
Huh?
Ah!
Teacher!
Shikata Nishu-san, are you okay?
Yes.
Teacher, are you okay?
I wasn't going back to the classroom.
Eh?
Eh...
But I didn't feel well.
Teacher, are you okay?
I'm okay.
Did you break the line?
Eh...
I'm going back to the classroom.
It's great, isn't it?
It's not that bad that Takakura-kun is bad, isn't it?
It's not like that.
Teacher, don't worry about it.
No, don't worry about it.
Teacher,
I always wanted to be a teacher who can always be a teacher.
It's different, teacher.
The teacher wanted me to be a teacher.
You wanted me to be a teacher?
Ah, the teacher was waiting for you to be a teacher like your mother.
Takakura-kun, you were doing a lot of things with the teacher.
I'm sure you did.
I wanted you to be a teacher like your mother.
Muka Muka is right.
If I don't do it, it's a little strange.
It's strange that I have to be a teacher who can always be a teacher.
I see.
Hmm.
If I had to work, I'm still a child.
It's a little strange that I have to work.
I didn't have to help you,
but I didn't have to protect you.
Muka Muka, you're back!
What are you doing?
I want to use my day.
Muka Muka!
Please, don't use it.
You can't do it, right?
Really.
It's a brush brush, right?
What if I hit it all?
Muka Muka!
Should I protect you?
Hey, teacher.
What I'm curious about is...
This school is a classroom, isn't it?
That's why I'm teaching you.
I don't like it either.
Muka Muka, I'm glad you're here.
You can become a teacher.
Muka Muka!
Uiba, you should go too.
Don't worry about it.
I'll be right back.
Senta!
What are you doing here?
I'm here!
Muka Muka Muka brought me here
and took me to the classroom.
What?
I'll do it if I hit it all.
This is it!
That's it.
You're back.
Don't stop.
I'll give it to you.
I'll give it to you two or three times.
Don't worry about it.
Please stop.
Senta!
Senta?
Is it Senta's teacher?
Yes.
It's Tan-nin's school.
Oh, it's a baby.
Senta!
I'll give you this baby's teacher.
Senta, please go to the classroom.
No, I'm Tan-nin.
No, I'm not Tan-nin's mother-in-law.
I won't go to Yusuke's school.
Mother-in-law?
That's right.
I thought you were a mother-in-law
and taught you how to do it.
Then, will you marry me?
What?
Senta!
I told you to go to the classroom.
Go to the classroom!
Oh, no!
It's a baby!
Senta!
I don't know how to say this.
That's right.
Senta,
I don't know about Hiroma's teacher.
I won't let you do this.
Please hide.
I won't let you do that.
You too, hide.
Muka Muka!
Muka Muka
BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG BANG B
Level 3
WASH-CHI-ONG-CHI-ONG-CHI-ONG-CHI-ONG-CHI-ONG!!
I don't want to lose to Matsuri!
I want to do my best!
I want to win and I'll do my best!
M-M-M-M-M-M...
You'll have no time to say that.
Next time, I'll be around on the مкامかっп smaller!
Matsuri!
M-M-M-M-M!
I'll be happy to...
I'm sorry, but I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.